turkeymmm.org 2016-05-21

# PRIVACY POLICY / MMM TURKEY — Official Website

Privacy Policy  
MMM Turkey respects the privacy of all its users and is committed to guard it in all respects. To find out how user information collected at the website is protected, please read the following private policy document.

Please make a note that MMM Turkey can make changes to this private policy from time to time. Keep checking this page to know more about the updated private policies.

Personal Information

We may collect the following information from our users:

Name  
Contact Information including email address  
Demographic Information such as postcode, preferences and interests  
Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

What We Do With The Information Collected

The information collected at the website is to present our valuable customers with better services and in particular for the following reasons:

Record Keeping for Internal Use.  
Improve our existing products and services.  
Send promotional emails periodically about new products, special offers or other information which users may find interesting.

Security

To make the process of collecting information secure, suitable physical and electronic procedures have been integrated with the website.

Links To Other Websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. We are not responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

Controlling Your Personal Information

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.When You use the Website, Company's servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) may collect information indirectly and automatically about Your activities on the Website; for instance by way of cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a user's browser from a web server and is eventually stored on a user's computer hard drive. This anonymous information is maintained distinctly and is not linked to the Personal Information You submit to "Company". Whether you want your web browser to accept cookies or not is up to you. If you haven't changed your computer's settings, most likely your browser already accepts cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience all features of the Website. You can also delete your browser cookies or disable them entirely, but this may significantly impact your experience with the Website and may make parts of the Website non functional or inaccessible. We recommend that you leave them turned on.

Modifying/Deleting Personal Information

Customers can modify or delete their personal information by sending an email to [support@turkey-mmm.net](mailto:support@turkey-mmm.net)

Opting Out Of Notifications From Business Name

In order to opt-out of future notifications from our company, customers can send an email to [support@turkey-mmm.net](mailto:support@turkey-mmm.net)
